老兄 这好奇怪
Man, this is weird.
你有没有发现脆脆船长的眉毛 长在他的帽子上
Ever realize Cap'n Crunch's eyebrows are on his hat?
这叫奇怪?
That's what's weird?
乔伊 那家伙当了40年的早餐片船长
Joey, the man's been captain of a cereal for the last 40 years.
咦!
Waaa-aaah!
干嘛
What?
汤匙 你舔完就放回去了
The spoon! You licked and, and you put.
舔完你就放回去了
You licked and you put.
对 怎么了
Yeah, so?
你不觉得这很恶心吗
Well, don't you see how gross that is?
就像是你用我的牙刷一样
I mean that's like you using my toothbrush.
你还用我的牙刷?
You used my toothbrush?
那是因为人家用红的那支去通排水孔了嘛
Well, that was only because I used the red one to unclog the drain.
红的那支是老子的
Mine is the red one!
我的老天爷 一发不可收拾啊
Oh, God! Can open, worms everywhere!
嘿 为什么牙刷不能共用
Hey, why can't we use the same toothbrush
肥皂就可以?
but we can use the same soap?
因为肥皂是肥皂 会自我清洁
Because soap is soap. It's self-cleaning.
行 那下次你冲凉的时候
Alright, well next time you take a shower
想想我最后洗哪儿 你又最先洗哪儿
think about the last thing I wash and the first thing you wash.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第16集
乔伊搬走了 Joey Moves Out
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：yjchandler
嘿      嘿
Hey.        Hey.
喔 瞧你们打扮的
Ooh, look at you fancy lads!
什么情况
What's the occasion?
知道在我那部剧里演昏迷不醒的那个人吗
Well, you know that guy that's on my show that's in a coma?
他做东
He's having a brunch.
好了 就等你了
Okay, I'm ready when you are.
搞定
Okey-doke.
真不敢相信你们真要去刺青
I can't believe you guys are actually getting tattoos.
等会儿 你们要去刺青?
Excuse me, you guys are getting tattoos?
对 但你不能告诉罗斯 因为我想给他个惊喜
Yes, but you can not tell Ross 'cause I want to surprise him.
喔噢 好奔放 你们准备刺什么
Wow, this is wild! What are you gonna get?
我要刺一朵百合
Um, I'm getting a lily.
纪念我妈 因为她叫莉莉
For my mom, 'cause her name's Lily.
算你命好 要是她叫大污点看你怎么办
Wow, that's lucky. What if her name was Big Ugly Splotch?
那你们要刺在哪里
So where you getting it?
肩膀上吧
I think on my shoulder.
什么
What?
你肩上有什么
What's on your shoulder?
呃 重担
Um, a chip.
是刺青 我要去刺青啦
A tattoo. I'm getting a tattoo
刺青? 为什么要去刺青
A tattoo? Why, why would you wanna do that?
嗨      嗨
Hi.        Hi.
你不觉得很酷吗
Well hey, you don't, you don't think they're kind of cool?
不 抱歉 我不觉得
No, sorry I don't.
怎么会有人花钱去搞个一辈子的伤痕
Tell me why would anyone pay someone to scar their body for life?
菲比 要是刺得不好怎么办
What if it doesn't come out right Phoebes?
那成什么了 我是说 就像你永远顶着个烂发型
Then it's like, I don't know, having a bad haircut all the time.
你们干嘛都盯着我
Why is everyone staring at me?
罗斯 过来在老爸的生日卡上签名
Ross, come sign this birthday card for Dad.
理查随时会到
Rich is gonna be here any minute.
哎哟 理查也要去派对啊
Oooh, Richard's going to the party too, huh?
他是我爸妈最要好的朋友 必须去
Well, he's my parents' best friend, he has to be there.
那今天打算告诉你爸妈你们俩的事吗
So, is today the day you're gonna tell them about you two?
是啊 为了我爸生日 我决定让他中风
Yeah, for my dad's birthday, I decided to give him a stroke.
不 我觉得你应该告诉他们
No, I think you should tell them.
不 我还不知道他爱我有多深
No, I don't even know how serious he is about me.
在搞清楚前 我什么也不说
Until I do, I'm not telling them anything.
很难说 我想他们不会介意的
I don't know, I don't think Mom and Dad would mind.
记得你9岁 理查30岁时 老爸常说...
Remember when you were 9 and Richard was 30, how dad used to say...
"天啊 真希望他们在一起"
"God, I hope they get together."
准备好了?
Alright, shall we?
等等
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait.
那什么
You know what?
罗斯 我们换下 你站中间
Ross, let's, let's switch places. You get in the middle.
不行不行 这一看就像是我们在隐瞒什么
No um, you know, unless this looks like we're trying to cover something up.
妹子
Monica, Monica
就算你骑着他进去他们也不会相信的
You could come in straddling him, they still wouldn't believe it.
我们来了
We're here!
嗨 孩子们      是孩子们
Oh hi, kids!        Uh, the children!
噢 宝贝儿
Hi,darling!
老爸 生日快乐      噢 谢谢
Happy birthday, Dad.        Oh thank you.
嗨 老妈
Hi ma.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
柏克医生载你们来 你们谢过他了吗
So, you kids thanked Dr.Burke for the ride?
妈 我想摩妮卡替我们两个谢过了
Uh, actually Mom, I think Monica thanked him for the both of us.
你们坐火车来的吗
So, you kids take the train in?
不 理查柏克载他们来的
No, Richard Burke gave them a ride.
说到他啊...
Um, speaking of whom...
我听说他在城里泡了个二十来岁的幼齿
I hear he's got some 20-year-old twinkie in the city.
手抖了 天啊 抱歉
Finger cramp! Oh, God, sorry.
妈 放着我来
Here, let me get that, Mom.
原来理查好这口啊
Sooo, Richard's shopping in the junior section?
还要讲那个吗
Are we still on that?
想想也知道她的智商肯定跟餐巾纸一样高
You just know she's got the IQ of a napkin.
说不定都不算漂亮
She's probably not even pretty.
只是够年轻 所以一切都还没下垂
Just young enough so that everything is still pointing up.
这地方超赞吧
Can you believe this place?
对啊 这公寓超赞
I know, this is a great apartment.
我刚去过浴室 两边墙上都有镜子
Ah, I was just in the bathroom, and there's mirrors on both sides of you.
尿尿的时候就像是有一排人一起尿
So when you're in there, it's like you're peeing with the Rockettes.
我的幻想成真了
Well, there's my fantasy come true.
真的
No, seriously.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 老兄 我们正在说你的公寓超棒的
Hey, we were just saying, great apartment man.
谢了 你要吗
Thanks. You want it?
什么
Uh?
我要搬去更大的公寓
Yeah, I'm moving to a bigger place.
你真的应该入手
You should definitely take this one.
你觉得我会住这么好吗
Yeah, can you see me in a place like this?
有何不可 你讨厌公园景观和挑高天花板吗
Why not? You hate park views and high ceilings?
来 我带你看看厨房
Come on, I'll show you the kitchen.
不用了伙计们 我今早在电视上...
Oh that'sall right fellas, I saw a kitchen this morning...
看过厨房了
on TV.
还是闭嘴好了
Stop talking. Okay!
拜托 快说嘛      就是呀 她真的只有20?
Come on, tell us!        Yeah, is she really 20?
我什么也不会说的
I am not telling you guys anything.
说嘛 理查 今天是我生日诶 让我过一下干瘾嘛
Come on Rich, it's my birthday. Let me live vicariously!
爸 你真的不会想那样做的
Dad, you really don't want to do that.
跟基友分享下你的中年危机嘛
Ahh, what's a little midlife crisis between friends?
杰克 放我一马吧
Jack, would you let it go?
我了解你在做什么 50岁的时候我买了辆保时捷
Look, I know what you're going through. When I turned 50, I got the Porsche.
你呢 也有了自己的小 "加速器"
You, you got your own little speedster.
各位 说真的 不是你们听到那样的
Guys, seriously, it is not like that.
这样
Tell you what.
找个周末 我车子借你 你的小...
Maybe one of these weekends you can borrow the car and I could...
爸 求你别说
Dad, I beg you not to finish that sentence!
干嘛啦 我开玩笑的嘛
What? I'm kidding!
我才不会让他碰我的保时捷呢
You know I'd never let him touch the Porsche.
瑞秋
Okay, Rach.
选哪朵百合 这朵还是那朵
Which lily? This lily or that lily?
我觉得...      我喜欢这朵
Well I...        I like this lily.
绽放得更灿烂 就像我妈
It's more open, you know, and that's like my Mom.
她有比较豁达 奉献的精神
She had a more open, giving spirit.
莱亨鸡!
Oh, Foghorn Leghorn!
金发妞儿 你到二号房
Alright, blond girl, you're in room two.
没那么金的妞儿 你跟我来
Not-so-blond girl, you're with me.
走吧
Here we go!
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
怎么不走
You're not going?
嗯
Uh-huh.
怎么了 是因为罗斯的话吗
What? Is it, is this because of what Ross said?
不是
No.
好吧 或许是的
Well, yeah, maybe.
真不敢相信
I don't believe this.
你们之间的关系难道就是罗斯占据着主导地位?
Is this how this relationship's gonna works? Ross equals boss?
拜托 又不是1922年了
I mean, come on, what is this, 1922?
1922年怎么了
What's 1922?
只是很久以前嘛
Just, you know, a long time ago.
那个年代的女人基本都得听男人的
When men used to tell women what to do a lot.
然后有了投票权 这是好事 不过听起来很可怕
And then there was suffrage, which was a good thing but it sounds horrible.
你到底要不要刺
Do you want this tattoo?
要啊 只是罗斯...
Yes I do, it's just that Ross is...
停停停 什么都要男朋友替你做主吗
OK, hey, hey. Is your boyfriend the boss of you?
不是
No.
那好 谁替你做主
Okay, who is the boss of you?
你?
You?
不 你该自己做主
No. You are the boss of you!
你现在就屁颠儿屁颠儿地进去
Now you march your heinie in there
把那颗心刺到屁股上
and get that heart tattooed on your hip!
去!
Go!
没事儿吧
How you doing?
我成幼齿了!
I'm a twinkie!
是吗 我可是个英雄
Really? I'm a hero.
这太纠结了
This is so hard.
我又何尝不是呢
Yeah, I know. I hate it too.
要不 我们公开吧
Look, maybe we should just tell them.
要不先跟你爸妈说吧
Maybe we should just tell your parents first.
我父母早就不在了
My parents are dead.
天啊 你命太好了
God, you are so lucky!
我是说... 你懂我的意思      我懂
I mean, well, you know what I mean.        I know, I know.
撑住 好吗
Just hang in there, okay?
我先出去 好吗
Okay, I'll go out first, all right?
好
Alright, alright.
茱蒂! 上厕所啊! 好肠胃啊!
Judy! Going to the bathroom! Good for you!
谢谢你给我动力 理查
Thank you Richard, I appreciate the support.
亲爱的
Honey.
看到我那哈蒙基勒博签名的球棒了吗
Honey, have you seen my Harmon Killebrew bat?
鲍勃不相信我有
Bob doesn't believe I have one.
没看到
I have no idea.
你知道理查在城里泡了个幼齿吗
Did you know Richard has a twinkie in the city?
我知道 他像是来第二春了
I know, he's like a new man.
就像是 "魔茧" 里的情景
It's like a scene from Cocoon.
我怎么也想不到 理查会跟一个小笨妹在一起
I just never would have pictured Richard with a bimbo.
显然他告诉强尼夏皮洛说 那个女孩不错
Apparently, he told Johnny Shapiro that she's quite a girl.
他还告诉强尼 他觉得自己爱上她了
In fact, he told Johnny that he thinks he's falling in love with her
是不是啊      跟你说 我没见他这么快乐过
Really?        I tell you, I've never seen him this happy.
那么 杰克...
So, Jack...
你有没有想过 找个年轻小妞儿来替代我
you ever think about trading me in for a younger model?
当然没有
Of course not.
有了你就等于有了两个二五佳人啊
With you, it's like I've got two 25-year-olds.
杰克 不要嘛
Oh, Jack, stop!
来嘛
Come on!
今天哥生日啊
It's my birthday!
能不说了吗
Can we drop this?
我对那家伙的公寓没兴趣
I am not interested in the guy's apartment.
拜托 我看到你欣赏他装饰的样子了
Oh, please, I saw the way you were checking out his moldings.
你想要
You want it.
我干嘛要另外一间公寓 啊?
Why would I want another apartment, huh?
我已经有我爱的公寓了
I've already got an apartment that I love.
是嘛 你偶尔这样 说说又不会死
It wouldn't kill you to say it once in a while.
好 你想听实话? 我的确在考虑
All right, you want the truth? I'm thinking about it.
什么      抱歉
What?        I'm sorry.
我都28了 还没一个人生活过
I'm 28, I've never lived alone
而现在我终于赚到足够的钱
and I'm finally at a place where I got enough money
可以让我不再需要室友了
that I don't need a roommate anymore.
切 哥也不需要室友啊
Whoa, whoa, whoa, I don't need a roommate either, okay?
哥一个人住这儿也负担得起
I can afford to live here by myself.
搞得好像哥每个礼拜都要请人来舔一遍餐具一样
You know I may have to bring in somebody once a week to lick the silverware.
你干嘛那么火大
What're you gettin' so bent out of shape for, huh?
我们又没说要永远住一起
It's not like we agreed to live together forever.
我们又不是动画片里的毕特和恩尼
We're not Bert and Ernie.
听着
Look, you know what.
如果你觉得是这样
If this is the way you feel
那也许你该搬过去
then maybe you should take it.
我是这么觉得      那也许你该搬过去!
Well that's how I feel.        Then maybe you should take it!
那好啊!
Well then maybe I will!
好啊!      好!
Fine with me!        Great!
这样你就能跟你真正的朋友好好过了
Then you'll be able to spend more quality time with your real friends
破汤匙!
the spoons!
谁还要饮料
Whose drink can I freshen?
该切蛋糕了
Almost time for cake!
妹子
Mon?
妹子 没事儿吧
Mon, are you okay?
还记得我发现的那盘爸妈主演的录像带吗
You remember that video I found of mom and dad?
记得 怎么了
Yeah?
我刚看了遍真人秀
Well, I just caught the live show.
嗨 怎么样      怎么了
Hey there.        What?
没什么 我刚听到你的好话
Nothing, I just heard something nice about you.
真的?
Humm, really?
理查 理查
Richard, Rich.
你儿子现在没女朋友吧      就我所知 没有
Your son isn't seeing anyone, is he?        Uh, not that I know of.
我在想 要不让他跟莫妮卡联系联系
Well, I was thinking, why doesn't he give Monica a call?
这... 是个主意
That... that's an idea.
其实 我已经有男朋友了
Well, actually, I'm already seeing someone.
喔?      喔?
Oh?        Oh?
啊呕...
Oh...
这孩子什么事都不说
She never tells us anything.
罗斯 你知道摩妮卡有男朋友了吗
Ross, did you know Monica's seeing someone?
妈 我身边有好多人
Mom, there are so many people in my life.
有些人在恋爱 也有些还是单身
Some are seeing people and some of them aren't.
那是水晶的吗
Is that crystal?
那个神秘男子是谁
So, who's the mystery man?
呃 他是个医生
Well, uh, he's a doctor.
不是博士?
A real doctor?
是 他是研究肉的
No, a doctor of meat.
他当然是个医生
Of course he's a real doctor.
他很英俊
And he's handsome.
人很好 我知道你会喜欢他的
And he's sweet, and I know you'd like him.
那不错...
Well that's wonderful, that...
我
I...
妈 没事的
Mom, it's okay.
没错 茱蒂
It is, Judy.
杰克!
Jack!
你能过来下吗
Could you come in here for a moment?
现在!
Now!
找到了      爸 交给我
Found it!        I'll take that, Dad.
你女儿跟理查看来是一对
It seems your daughter and Richard are something of an item.
不可能 他不是在城里有个幼齿嘛
That's impossible. He's got a twinkie in the city.
爸 我就是那个幼齿
Dad, I'm the twinkie.
你就是那个幼齿?      她不是幼齿!
You're the twinkie?        She's not a twinkle!
好吧 听着 这是我至今谈过最棒的恋爱...
Al-alright, l-look you guys, this is the best relationship I've been in...
拜托 这叫谈恋爱?
Oh please! A relationship?
对 就是谈恋爱!
Yes, a relationship!
你们听好了 我为这个男人痴狂
For your information, I am crazy about this man.
真的?
Really?
真的
Yes.
老子过生日居然要站在这儿听你们放屁?
Am I supposed to stand here and listen to this on my birthday?
爸 这对我是件好事
Dad, dad this is a good thing for me, you know
而且你自己也说 你没见过理查这么快乐过
and you even said yourself, you've never seen Richard happier.
我什么时候说的
When did I say that?
楼上浴室里 就在你对老妈毛手毛脚前!
Upstairs in the bathroom, right before you felt up Mom!
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
祝杰克生日快乐
Happy birthday, dear Jack
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
噢 看着好漂亮 我好喜欢
Oh it looks so good! Oh I love it.
对啊 我也好喜欢 菲比 真高兴你逼我刺了
I know, so do I! Phoebe I'm so glad you made me do this.
好了 让我看看你的
Okay, let me see yours.
呃 你的再让我看一眼
Okay, let's see yours again.
菲比 我的才看过 让我看看你的
Phoebe we just saw mine, let me see yours.
好
Oh, okay.
噢 不
Oh, no!
不见了 好奇怪啊
Oh it's gone! That's so weird.
不知道去哪里了
I don't know how, where it went.
你没刺?      没
You didn't get it?        No.
你干嘛不刺
Why didn't you get it?
抱歉 真的很抱歉
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
菲比 你怎么可以这么对我 这全是你的主意
Phoebe, how could you do this to me? This was your idea!
我知道 我本来要刺的 可是他进来时拿着针
I know, I know, and I was gonna get it, but he came in with this needle
你知道他们是用针刺的吗
and uh, di-did you know they do this with needles?
真的? 我可从来没听过啊
Really? You don't say.
因为我的是喵星人舔上去的!
Because mine was licked on by kittens!
嘿      嘿
Hey.        Hey.
嘿 听着 今天的事我很抱歉...
Hey listen, I'm sorry about what happened...
我也是      是啊
Yeah me too.        I know, yeah.
好啦      好啦
Yeah.        Yeah.
那我们是抱一下还是...
So do we need to hug here or...
不用了吧      对
No, we're all right.        Yeah.
我有东西给你
So I got you something.
塑胶汤匙
Plastic spoons!
太棒了      随你怎么舔 好基友
Great!        Lick away, my man.
这在我的新家会很管用 先应付应付
These will go great in my new place, you know, till I get real ones.
什么
What?
我不能老是用这东西
I can't use these forever.
我是说 这不环保
I mean, let's face it, they're no friend of the environment.
不不不 我是说 你说什么新家?
No-no, I mean what, what's this about your new place?
我要搬出去 我们谈论过的
I'm moving out, like we talked about.
我不知道你是认真的
Well I didn't think that was serious.
我以为我们只是在吵架
You know, I thought that was just a fight.
对啊 我们确实吵架了
Well, it was a fight...
有根有据的 记得吗
based on serious stuff, remember?
有关我从来没一个人生活过
About how I never lived alone or anything?
我想这样对我有好处 能帮助我成长...
I think it would be good for me, you know, help me to grow or...
之类的
whatever.
那好吧
Well, there you go.
嘿 这事你能接受吗
Hey, are you cool with this?
我不想让你觉得进退维谷
I mean, I don't wanna leave you high and dry.
嘿 我本来也没有好到哪儿去
Hey, no, I've never been lower or wetter.
我能有什么事 我准备把你房间...
I'll be fine. I'll just turn your, uh...
改成游戏室之类的
bedroom into a game room or something, you know.
把桌上足球放到里面
Put the foosball table in there.
等等 那桌子为什么归你
Woah. Why do you get to keep the table?
我付了一半的钱
I did pay for half of it.
对 但另外一半是我付的
Yeah. And uh, I paid for the other half.
行 那我们来一局 谁赢归谁
Alright I'll tell you what, I'll play you for it.
好 说定了
All right, you're on.
哥抽个两分钟出来虐虐你也无妨
I can take two minutes out of my day to kick your ass.
哥射进的球 会比你妹被射的次数还多
Your little men are gonna get scored on more times than your sister.
嘿! 嘿! 嘿! 嘿!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
哪个妹妹
Which sister?
你后悔我告诉他们吗
So are you sorry that I told them?
不会 反正我跟你爸好久没去跑步了
No, it's been a long time since your dad and I went running.
噢
Oh.
噢 嘿 你们刺了吗 让我瞧瞧
Oh. Well, did you get it? Let me see.
罗斯在吗      不在 他去买披萨了
Is Ross here?        No he went out for pizza.
好 抓紧时间
Okay, really quick, okay.
好漂亮
That's great!
很有品味
Very tasteful.
要看我的吗      好啊
Wanna see mine? Wanna see mine?        Yes!
什么 你又没刺
What? You didn't get one.
好 那这是什么
Okay, well then, what is this?
我们在看什么
What are we looking at?
那颗蓝色的雀斑?
That blue freckle?
拜托 这是我的刺青
Okay, that's my tattoo.
那不是刺青 那什么也不是
That is not a tattoo. That is a nothing.
我好不容易把她弄回去刺
I finally got her in the chair,
结果人家的针还没碰到她
he barely touched her with the needle
她就尖叫着跳起来 逃了回来
she jumped up screamed and that was it.
好了
Okay, hi!
你们听好了 这正是我想要的刺青
For your information, this is exactly what I wanted.
这是个从很远的地方看到的地球
This is a tattoo of the Earth as seen from a great, great distance.
我妈从天堂看我就是这样的
It's the way my mother sees me from heaven.
简直胡说八道
Oh, what a load of crap!
那就是一个点
That is a dot!
你妈正在天堂大叫说
Your mother's in heaven going,
"老娘的百合呢 你个胆小鬼!"
"Where the hell's my lily, you wuss!"
菲比 那不叫刺青! 这才叫刺青!
Okay, Phoebe, that is not a tattoo! This is a tattoo!
你去刺青了?
You got a tattoo?
算是吧
Maybe.
只是很小一个 菲比把全世界都刺上了
But just a little one. Phoebe got the whole world!
让我看看
Well, let me see.
怎么样
Well?
非常...
Well, it's really...
性感
sexy.
我没想过可以这样 但是...
I wouldn't have thought it would be, but...
哇
wow!
真的?
Really?
真的 那么
Yeah, so uh
会酸痛吗 还可以做运动吗
is it sore or can you do stuff?
可以吧
I guess.
嘿 给我们留点披萨
Hey, save us some pizza.
把球传出来!
Get it out of the corner!
传球! 传球!
Pass it! Pass it!
别跟你的队员讲话了!
Stop talking to your men!
得分!
Yes!
桌子是哥的了
And the table is mine.
恭喜了
Congratulations.
嘿 你们还是会来看我的吧
Hey, you guys are still gonna come visit me, right?
当然 你有那么大的电视
Oh, yeah! You got the big TV
我们会常去的
We'll be over there all the time.
不在这里的时候我们才会去
Except when we are here.
我知道你只是搬到上城区 但我还是会很想念你的
I know you're just moving uptown, but I'm really gonna miss you.
对啊 你怎么能不住我们对面了呢
I know, how can you not be across the hall anymore?
就是 以后谁来吃光我们的东西
Yeah, who's gonna eat all of our food,
谁来占用我们的电话 谁来...
and tie up our phone lines and...
那是我胸罩吗
Is that my bra?
你拿我胸罩干嘛
What the hell are you doing with my bra?
噢 不 不是你想的那样
Oh no-no, it's uh, it's not what you think.
我们以前用它把水球弹到屋顶上
We uh, we used it to, you know, fling water balloons off the roof.
记得吗
Remember that?
那些初中生连马路对过都弹不到
Those junior high kids couldn't even get theirs accross the street.
嗯 我记得
Yeah, I remember.
嘿 我们把剩下的搬车上去吧
Hey, let's bring the rest of these down to the truck.
谢谢
Thanks
那 你要我...
So, uhh, em, you want me to uh...
帮你把足球桌搬下去吗
give you a hand with the foosball table?
不了
Nah.
留着吧 你要好好练练
You keep it. You need the practice.
谢了
Thanks.
那么...
So...
我想 就这样吧
I guess this is it.
是啊
Yeah, right, yeah.
大概吧
I guess so.
听着...
Listen, uh...
我不知道什么时候能再见到你
I don't know when am I gonna see you again?
我想 今晚在咖啡馆就可以
Well, I'm guessing uh, tonight at the coffee house.
对 也是
Right, yeah. Okay.
那 保重      好
Um, take care.        Yeah.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧